{
    "id": "57dedef1b1ca4cc586c3c9e73fcdc561",
    "title": "Verb Forms Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ………………….. the Minister tomorrow.",
            "description": "We use the present continuous to talk about future events if the arrangement already exists. ",
            "answers": [
                "see",
                "am seeing",
                "will see"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2588dbcf2a7d49828c9a156551d070d7"
        },
        {
            "question": "What are you …………………. this weekend?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "doing",
                "done"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "aa34318767b845229660f822ccdcf44f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………… thirty-seven next month.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will turn",
                "would turn",
                "turned"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "926226a742b7425184f96907e0297338"
        },
        {
            "question": "Buses ……………….. every five minutes.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "leave",
                "will leave",
                "are leaving"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8c129d2e37f840a29198ff61c05bdef3"
        },
        {
            "question": "This time tomorrow I ..................... my exam.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will write",
                "will be writing",
                "am writing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "60909b4330eb4354a04c62c0602d2ed0"
        },
        {
            "question": "I knew she ………………… arrive before long.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ec71cff07d6a4c5d8c5b8dc739bb7794"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will phone you when I ………………… time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "will have",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a6a62dc013e64248a3a40d26e75bf715"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will follow you wherever you ………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "are going",
                "have gone"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "16081b67bce2498897be791ed48220c0"
        },
        {
            "question": "What ……………….. we ……………….. for dinner?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do, have",
                "are, having",
                "will, be having"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7c8c2de3a927425f83536591b8ea871a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………… the money on the 20th.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am needing",
                "will need",
                "would need"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c6692156a86e42199b7e3a05e7f38094"
        }
    ]
}